♪ In the not-too-distant future
♪ Next Sunday A.D.
♪ There was a guy named Joel
♪ Not too different
from you or me
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place
♪ But his bosses didn't like him
♪ So they shot him into space
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst we can find
♪ La-la-la
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And we'll monitor his mind
♪ La-la-la
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La-la-la
♪ Because he used
those special parts
♪ To make his robot friends
♪ Robot Roll Call
♪ Cambot
♪ Gypsy
♪ Tom Servo
♪ Croooow
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-La-la
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show,
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000
(guitar twang)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Now listen, are you
sure you guys wanna go,
the experiment's
just about to start.
- Ah, the experiments bite.
It's all do dull and so...
Banal.
- Yeah Joel, this place
is for losers and squares.
Stick around here
and you're headed for
nowhere on a rocket sled, baby.
Uh, no offense, of course.
- Oh, no.
Oh hi everybody, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
I'm Joel Robinson, still
stuck up here in space
and this is Gypsy.
- Hi!
- And my other two robots,
Tom Servo and Crow,
have decided to run
away from home and
go live on the other
side of the ship.
- Alright, we're gonna
get going then, Joel.
And please, don't embarrass
yourself by following us, okay?
- Oh no, I won't.
This is your deal.
I can see you've got everything.
Uh, what's this right
here, Tom, in your hand?
- Oh, I made a boomerang
to hunt wild animals.
- Oh, smart.
Oh, well, see you later.
- [Tom And Crow] Okay, bye.
♪ I was born under
a wandering star--
- They'll be back.
- Yeah.
Uh, hey, Magic Voice,
you want to give us
a status report on
how they're doing?
- [Magic Voice] They
are fifty yards away.
They have stopped, they
appear to be arguing.
Crow has put down
his pack and is
hitting Tom Servo
on the shoulder.
Tom is crying.
They're headed back.
Commercial Sign now.
- You were right, Gypsy.
- Yeah.
- We'll be right back.
(theme music)
- We're back, we forgive you.
- Yeah, what's for lunch?
- I thought you guys were
going to run away and live on
the other side of the ship?
- Yeah.
- Uh, we did.
We're done.
It got way too
built up over there.
- Yeah.
So, what's the movie today?
- I don't know.
Oh, Shari Lewis and
Lambchop are calling.
- Well Joel, we're introducing
a new feature here today.
Here's a hint.
Remember Lost Continent?
Remember rock climbing?
(evil chuckling)
- Oh, who could ever forget
rock climbing, huh Clay?
(chuckles)
Well now, along the same
lines, we've come up with
something new, something
we like to call...
Sandstorm, sandstorm!
- It's all part of a new
program we like to call...
- [Both] Deep hurting.
Deep hurting!
- But that's for later.
You run along and do your
invention exchange, Joel.
- Sandstorm.
(chuckling)
- Our invention
exchange is Freakout!
(blowing)
- Freakout, huh?
Cute, but it hardly
qualifies as an invention.
- Oh did I forget to mention,
it's all part of a kit
and with refill
sets, you can make...
- [All] Super Freakout!
(all yelling)
(psychedelic music)
- Well, we're not much for
freaking out, are we Frank?
- Trails...
Beautiful trails...
(all shouting)
- He'll take you up,
he'll take you down.
- Freakout and Super Freakout,
by Four Dead in Ohio Arts.
- Tin soldiers, Nixon
coming sold separately.
- What do you think, sirs?
- I'm a scientist.
I don't think, I observe!
- See me, feel me, touch me!
- Oh great, you've triggered
a freakout in Frank!
Anyway, rock climbing was a
cool groove compared to...
- Sandstorm!
(coughing)
Sandstorm!
- That's right, Joel,
what Wishbone Ash here
is trying to tell you is
that our invention exchange
this week--
- [Both] Deep hurting.
- Is so beautiful,
so insidious, so...
(strange noise)
That's right, that
it's actually woven
into the tapestry of
today's experiment.
- Hercules Against the Moon Men.
- And it all culminates in...
- [Both] Deep hurting.
- But we don't wanna
give too much away.
You run along, Joel.
Push the button, Frank.
- I am the button!
(alarms blaring)
(shouting gibberish)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors opening)
(dramatic music)
(Tom humming)
- [Tom] Big Alan
Steel brings it home!
- [Crow] Alan Steel is
Steve Allen's pen name.
- [Joel] You know, Herc is
just flat against any moon men.
- [Tom] He's going up against
the Unification Church, I think.
Heh, the moon men.
- [Crow] Filmed against
the heart muscle.
- [Joel] Oh, hold the pesto.
- [Tom] Man, all these
people are foreigners!
- [Crow] Hey!
- [Joel] Carlo's been stealing
tone poems from Stravinsky.
- [Tom] Sounds like
it, doesn't it?
(humming)
N.C. Stu-stu-studio.
N.C. Stu-stu-studio, uh!
- [Joel] Nike, just film it.
- [Crow] Heh, that's Larry
Mondello's uncle, by the way.
♪ Wee Luigi Mondello
- [Tom] Gentilomo, I abhor you,
please don't make this film.
- [Narrator] That fatal
night, a fiery mass
dropped from the sky onto Earth.
- [Joel] Skylab!
- [Narrator] Causing
the mountain of Samar
to erupt and burn
everything around it,
leaving nothing but a wasteland.
- [Crow] Really made a mess.
- [Joel] Sad, really.
- [Narrator] In the
bowels of the mountain,
a new and monstrous
life was formed.
- [Tom] Oh, gross.
- [Narrator] From that day
on, the people of Samar,
in order to survive, were
forced to offer their children
as a sacrifice to the
hungry Mountain of Death.
- [Joel] Hey, you got change
for an eight-year-old?
(pained chuckling)
I'm kidding.
- [Crow] War comes to
the Land of Dairy Queen!
♪ Hi-ho, hi-ho, it's
off to death we go
(slaves crying)
- [Crow] Thank you sir,
may I have another?
(crying and shouting)
- [Joel] Ah, we don't
wanna get sacrificed today.
- [Tom] You kids quit whining
or I'll turn this thing around!
- [Crow] Ah, early
Disney employees.
- [Tom] Oh, not through the
puddles, that's not nice.
- [Crow] Not that way, R2.
(whistling)
You'll be breaking
down in no time.
(sad whistling)
- [Joel] Jim Henson's
Exodus Babies.
(Tom chuckling)
- [Crow] I am the mighty Pavog!
(slaves screaming)
- [Tom] Please enter
your PIN number.
- [Joel] Oh, they're taking
the slaves for a drag.
- [Tom] No, we don't wanna
see Siegfried and Roy, no, no!
- [Joel] Behind the green door.
- [Crow] Boy, those kids are
really bad at tug-of-war.
- [Tom] I'll say.
- [Crow] Got it all screwed up.
- [Joel] Shouldn't they have
a better loading system?
I mean, you know.
- [Tom] I think so.
- [Tom] Okay, people, come on.
Two, three, and step and
struggle and step ball change,
and struggle, two,
three, four and
death hands, people,
death hands, come on!
Step struggle step and change.
- [Joel] Go into the light!
- [Crow] Hey, if you
think this is bad,
this is only purgatory!
- [Tom] Well, you
know, personally I
think they're in Limbo.
- [Joel] Rush Limbo?
- [Tom] D'oh, no!
That would be more like hell.
- [Crow] Come on, move ahead.
You pay at the second window!
Come on.
- [Tom] Uh-oh, mom's here, run!
There they go.
- Queen Samara, your poor
people can no longer endure
the endless human sacrifice...
- [Tom] Man, she has huge legs!
- And that before you I
served your late father
with the same devotion.
- [Joel] Check it out,
it's a life-size
achievement award.
- Listen to the desperate
cries of the mothers of Samar,
the screams of the
innocent victims.
- [Crow] But don't
listen to Neil Diamond.
- [Tom] Please.
- You cannot, you must not
allow this wanton slaughter.
- [Joel] Okay, next!
- Old enough to
remember what happened
during my father's reign.
Long before--
- [Crow] Hey, it's Jody from
Family Affair, all grown up!
- I remember.
- [Tom] Hi-keeba.
- The fate that overtook
those who dared to rebel
is even worse than
the destiny we face.
But this has changed!
- [Samara] Changed?
- Yes!
There exists a man,
one who'll soon move.
One whose courage and whose
strength have allowed him
to overcome any
danger that threatens.
- And do you think
he'll be able to conquer
those who reign on
the Mountain of Death?
(gobbling)
- Yes.
If he were to lead us,
your people would succeed--
(gobbling)
- Silence you old fool!
You'll only destroy
yourself, and me too.
- Samara, my queen,
I beseech you.
- [Tom] I explore you.
- So don't take it away.
- [Samara] I
command you to stop!
- Send for this man,
he lives in Cherib.
Send for him before
it's too late.
- [Crow] Okay,
what's his number?
- Your people are tired.
- You dare to make threats.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- Get out or for you
it'll be too late!
- [Joel] He's a
chest of drawers.
- [Crow] Is that my puddle?
- [Joel] Fine, jerkface.
- [Tom] What was that?
- [Joel] Nothing.
- [Crow] Okay, you're shapely!
- [Tom] Hi, I'm a chocolate bar.
Break off bits of me
and enjoy me all day.
- [Joel] Wow, she
looks like she was
carved to go on
the bow of a ship.
- The man from Cherib
is about to arrive.
They must be meeting secretly.
- What's his name?
- Hercules.
- [Tom] Yep, that's my
cue, big Alan Steel.
Splash me on in the morning,
wear the great smell
of me all day long.
- [Joel] Look, he's riding
on the horse's neck.
That's gotta hurt.
♪ I'll be comin' round
the mountain when I come
(humming)
- [Joel] Huh-huh, it's a living.
(goofy chuckling)
- [Crow] His body
makes me feel funny.
♪ In the big country,
dreams stay with you
- [Tom] Oh no, this next
part here's a little tricky.
Gotta go between
some trees here.
- [Joel] Hey, he took
the good tablecloth.
♪ Oh, who's the guy
and he's got big pecs
♪ And they call him Herc, ho
- [Tom] I must have
missed the exit.
No, I don't see the highway.
♪ Hercu-lee, Hercu-la
♪ Hercu-lee,
Hercu-la-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
♪ Hercu-lee, Hercu-laa,
♪ My backpack's filled with pecs
(chuckling)
- [Joel] You know, the best
scenic overlooks are the
scenic overlooks that aren't
marked as scenic overlooks.
- [Tom] That's true.
- [Crow] You know, it all starts
lookin' the same after a while.
- [Tom] Pretty much, whoa!
I hate Mondays!
- [Crow] Whoa, sorry
Herc, I tripped.
(yelling)
- [Joel] I meant to do that.
- [Crow] Hey, he's got
his thong on upside-down.
- [Tom] Oh no!
- [Joel] Not the twins!
- [Tom] Oh, Rob Reiner, no!
There he goes.
- [Crow] It's a scrum!
- [Joel] Oh, he's wearing
his swim trunks, look.
- [Crow] Father Murphy, no!
♪ When you're a Greek,
you're a Greek all the way
♪ From your last cigarette
(chuckles)
- [Joel] Gymkata.
- [Crow] Ha-ha, meet Sammy
Spear and his orchestra!
♪ I enjoy being a guy, yeah
- [Tom] Clean-up on aisle five!
Heh, I love that one.
- [Joel] Well, time
for my Snickers.
- [Crow] (whinnying)
What took you so long?
I'm only kidding, Herc.
- [Tom] It's not nice
to fool Mother Nature!
(high-pitched noise)
- [Joel] Oh no, the
smoke alarm again.
Every time I heat a glazed
donut in the microwave.
- [Tom] Oh, it's Hamlet's dad.
Run, Phil!
- [Crow] Oh that's
right, it's Thursday.
- [Joel] It's a vision
of a Mexican wrestler!
- [Crow] El Santo,
I'm glad you're here.
- [Tom] The Ghost
of Christmas Cuckoo.
- Hercules is alive.
He escaped from the
trap you set for him.
- [Joel] He chewed his leg off.
- But how could he avoid death
at the hands of
my best soldiers?
- You underestimated that man.
- [Crow] Shop Red Owl.
- As long as he stays
alive, he remains a threat
to that destiny
written in the stars.
We will not be able
to leave the mountain.
- [Joel] We will
not be undersold!
- [Moon Man] And
you will not become
the most powerful
woman on Earth.
- I promise you he will die.
*theme music)
- [Darix] Billis!
- My love!
- [Tom] Say...
- [Crow] Who told him
that was a good look?
- When are we
going to be able to
meet openly in
front of everyone?
I'm going to speak
to your sister!
- [Joel] Not in
that, you're not!
- Why are you so frightened?
After your own, my family
is the most noble in Samar.
- I've tried many times.
- [Tom] Oh, cross
your legs please.
- To speak to her of our
future and of our love,
but I've always found
Samara strangely hostile.
- [Crow] Yeah, but what a bod.
- Your sister brings
only sadness to everyone.
- That's not fair to her.
- Face the facts, the
people are suffering.
They want to free
themselves from fear.
They want to destroy the
monsters of the mountain
and now they might
be able to do it.
- [Tom] Is he a drum major?
- But the queen
is still opposed.
- To fight against
the mysterious power
of the monsters,
no one has ever
tried to do that.
I'm frightened, Darix.
- [Joel] I'm
frightened Derick too.
- I don't intend to lose you.
I love you, and I
intend to marry you.
As soon as possible.
- [Crow] After I finish school.
(muffled talking)
- [Crow] This is my
little friend Gorgon.
Say hello to the folks, Gorgon.
- [Joel] Hello, folks.
- [Tom] Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
- Are you Hercules?
- [Crow] I could be.
- Yes, who are you?
What do you want?
- I'm to lead you to
the man who sent for you.
- [Tom] She's a Smurf!
ú- Alright, up with you.
- [Joel] I think I'm
sitting on the saddle horn.
- As a boy, you weren't
very convincing.
- I'm Agar, daughter
of Claudius.
- What made your father
send a girl to meet me,
and a child at that?
- I have no brothers and
my father trusts only me.
- [Tom] Oh, oh--
Stop talking so fast.
- For the cause of
liberty and justice,
I'm ready to do anything.
- Even to fight?
- That too, if it's necessary.
- [Joel] Would you fight me?
- Let's go.
I'll take you into Samar by
a route that only I know.
- [Joel] By the way,
do you ever bathe?
Ugh.
- [Tom And Crow]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
- [Joel] Pizza, pizza.
- [Crow] It is bassoon!
- [Agar] Come.
- [Tom] Hey, this is nice.
(gasps)
- It's the queen, we must hide.
- [Joel] Uh, okay.
- [Tom] This is wild, I swear.
- [Crow] Hey, how long do
I have to hide back here?
Oh...
- [Tom] Shh!
- I saw you leaving the
city at daybreak, Agar.
- I'm greatly
honored that my queen
should take the trouble
to watch over me.
- If I do so, it's
for your own good.
(Tom hissing)
And you are young, so young.
You should be more prudent.
- [Crow] Wow, smells
like Gold's Gym in here.
- [Tom] Witch, rhymes with.
- [Joel] What was that?
- [Tom] Nothing,
nothing, nothing.
Oh, it's the Mike
Douglas Show set.
- Hercules, she's gone.
You can come out now.
- [Joel] I knew that.
- [Crow] I'm writing a spec
script for Aristophanes.
- Let me thank you, Hercules,
for answering my prayer.
- It was my father's friendship
for you that brought me here.
- Did anyone see you?
- [Tom] Gotta go, gotta
go, gotta go, gotta...
- I was ambushed by
a band of ruffians.
They must have mistaken me for
a rich merchant
with sacks of gold.
I changed their minds for them.
- Bandits!
- [Joel] Hadji, Jonny, Race!
- That's strange, all the
roads that lead to Samar
are always carefully guarded.
Did you get a chance to
see who their leader was?
- [Crow] Was it a
guy with a big hat?
- He had a big black
beard and there was a
long ugly scar running
down his cheek.
- [Tom] Neck
cracked like celery.
- That's Taris.
- Who is he?
- One of Mogol's soldiers, and
the right arm of the queen.
- The queen?
Is she against you?
- Yes, I'm afraid so.
- [Crow] (imitating
buzzer) Uh, Sarah,
could you get us some coffee?
- The king was dying, the
last thing he said to me was--
(Tom groaning)
Watch over Samara,
guide her, call to her.
At the time, I thought my
task would be an easy one.
However...
- [Tom] So, if it--
- Only arrogance.
- [Tom] Oh, well--
- Or limitless pride.
- [Tom] Well, you see--
I tried to--
- Together with
unrestrained ambition.
- [Tom] But I don't know--
- I tried to induce her
to rebel against them--
- [Tom] Well sure, but--
- [Joel] You lost me!
- Every third new moon,
our youth is decimated
by a sacrifice that's
barbaric and inhuman.
The next sacrifice
takes place tomorrow.
Hercules--
- [Crow] Let's have
cookies outside.
- That's why I sent for you.
You've always been a great
fighter in the cause of justice
and you've always
been the victor.
Will you lead the
people of Samar?
- [Tom] No!
Oh, sorry, I mean yes.
- That's what I'm
here for, Claudius.
- [Joel] That, and I
wanna get a kick-ass tan.
- But you won't be alone.
You will have every
courageous man in the city
beginning with the
young Prince Darix,
the cousin of the queen.
(gibbering)
- [Crow] Wow, she
cleaned up real nice.
- Your daughter's as
courageous as she is beautiful.
- [Joel] Will Leona win
the heart of Hercules?
- [Tom] Let go,
Daddy, that's enough.
- I would have chosen
a more tranquil
life for her, without fear.
- Have no regrets, Father.
Think of all the
innocent lives we'll save
if we win our fight.
- - [Crow] Uh yes,
Hercules, still here?
- In leaving the palace it
wouldn't be wise for you
to take the same route
by which you entered.
- [Tom] Oh, out the back
door for the Herc, huh?
- I'll show you the way
through the secret tunnel.
Follow me.
- [Joel] Could you put
some lotion on my back?
- [Tom] There we go, like it?
I just had it put in.
Don't know how I got
along without it.
Back here is the grill
and the open fireplace.
(mumbles)
- [Joel] Hmm, I miss him.
Well, maybe not.
- [Tom] (gasps) A film crew!
(gasps)
- [Joel] Porky's 2.
- This is the moment.
- [Crow] Shave your head
and work your way north.
- [Tom] Oh, what's
that code again?
Oh...
- [Joel] Looks like they're
on a Doctor Who set.
- [Crow] So it just goes
on and on like this, huh?
- [Tom] My thighs are
really rubbing today.
- [Joel] Oh, I hate this
mall, you can't find anything.
- [Tom] Then I put in this shag,
I got bumper pool in the back.
Of course, Verna's put up
some jam, jellies and compotes
and you see...
(all humming sneaking music)
- [Crow] You ever get
silverfish down here?
- We're almost there.
- [Tom] Good. Where?
- [Joel] They should
have put the restrooms
closer to the dining room.
- [Tom] Well it's
not hard to find
once you know your way
around, and of course--
Agh!
(groaning)
Oh I forgot I put
that in, dagnabit.
- [Crow] That too,
watch the fl--
Oh, shoot. Sorry.
- [Joel] Darn kids!
- [Tom] Oh no,
Archie just flushed!
- [Joel] Kinda looks like
they're in a Starburst ad.
- [Crow] Not a bath,
it's not July yet.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the most mystifying and
mysterious booby trap illusion!
- The Malaysian
booby trap illusion!
- The most mystifying
booby trap of all!
- The biggest booby
trap ever made!
- That's right, it's the
biggest, bouncing-est...
- [Both] Booby trap.
- That ever bounced a--
- Booby!
(giggling)
- Okay..
- Booby-ooby
(laughing)
- Okay you two, hey,
I need your attention.
Two lovely assistants, please,
let's try to keep it together
and present this
major stage illusion.
- Please forgive us, we're
behaving like a couple of boobs.
(laughing)
- Oh come on, be
mature, come on.
- Come on, it's just
the name of a bird.
- Okay, okay.
We will now perform
the amazing illusion
whose name we're
not allowed to say.
- Booby.
- Okay.
As you can see, these
are real steel walls
with razor-sharp knives
set in and poised and ready
to pierce Joel's tender skin.
Let 'er rip!
(grunting)
- The booby trap illusion!
The amazing booby...
Ta-da!
Now we lift back the walls.
- Okay.
(grunting)
- Ta-da!
- Pretty good.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I actually feel
not too bad, you know,
for my experience, what
with those steel knives
penetrating my flesh and all.
You know, it could
be a lot worse.
- [Magic Voice] Joke is
taxiing on the marker
and is cleared for
landing on Runway 52.
- Yeah, you know, when a person
goes through an experience
like that, you imagine
something to go wrong.
I mean, you know, I'm only
human but with those knives
coming in and all, not really
even hurting me in the least,
you'd think something would
go wrong but it didn't.
(muffled laughter)
Funny really.
- [Magic Voice] Gear is
locked and joke should be
touching down in just a moment.
- Are you sure about that, Joel?
Is there anything you need?
- Not really, I mean, I
went through the experience
with the knives and all.
Maybe a glass of water.
- [Magic Voice]
Joke is now landing.
- By all means.
(muffled laughing)
(laughing)
- [Magic Voice] The
joke has landed.
Please remain seated with your
seat in the upright position
until the seatbelt
light is turned off.
This has been the
Satellite of Love,
inviting you to laugh
at least once a day.
It's fun.
We'll be back after this word
(speech muffled by echoes)
- Ah, I gotta take a leak!
(laughing)
(laughing in unison)
- [Both] Deep hurting.
Deep hurting!
(theme music)
(laughing)
- [Joel] Okay, I get the
hint, I'll bathe more!
Trog, with Joan Crawford.
- [Crow] There she is.
- [Tom] Irish Spring, manly yes,
but demigods love it too.
- [Joel] Hey, fur
kills, I guess.
- [Crow] A-ha-ha, Dino no!
(Tom yipping)
- [Tom] Oh Hercules,
he likes you.
Ooh there's a good
monkey monster,
who's a good ape monster?
- [Crow] Oh, it's Robert Bly.
- [Tom] Da-huh?
- [Joel] Bigtooth.
(Tom grunting)
- [Crow] Get your paws off
me, you damn dirty ape!
Or whatever you are.
- [Tom] Young
monster, you're going
to the orthodontist
whether you like it or not!
[Joel] Trumpy, you're angry!
- [Tom] Oh brother, this
guy smells worse than I do.
- [Crow] Take it
back, take it back!
(monster screaming)
(Tom growling)
- [Joel] Oh now
what, look at this.
- [Tom] Will Hercules be
able to bend the bars?
Will the ape regain
consciousnesS?
Tune in again next week.
- [Joel] you know, if he wasn't
so into that frontal shop,
he probably could
slip through sideways.
- [Tom] Yeah, you're right.
- [Crow] Must be those
new hardened steel bars.
- [Joel] You know, I think
this exercise is working.
I can feel it here and here.
- [Tom] Well he's
strong, bar none.
Get it, bar...
Sorry.
- [Joel] Boy, it's a
lot easier this way.
- [Crow] Super Bob Vila.
- [Tom] Whoa, it's my
manager, better hide.
- [Joel] Sounds kinda
like Eraserhead.
Man-made chickens,
but they're new!
- Agar!
- [Tom] Hey, wanna
go to Snow Days?
Just wondering if you...
(sobbing)
- [Crow] It's not like
he was your dad or any--
Oops.
- [Tom] Oh, awkward.
- I couldn't do
anything to save him.
I'll never forgive
myself for it.
- [Joel] You think it's easy
to find skin bronzer in here?
- We were being spied
on by Queen Samara.
I ran after you to warn you.
- [Crow] I think you
got a deer tick there.
- I only got here
in time to hear
the last words of my father.
- [Tom] Now Dad's a kebab!
- He ordered me to lead
you to the rendezvous
where he had
intended to take you.
You must join the others
so that they'll know
you're still alive
and won't abandon us.
- You know better than that.
I could never abandon you, Agar.
- Thank you, Hercules.
- [Joel] No, thank you.
- On your shoulders rests the
future of the people of Samar.
- [Crow] I know.
- I have great
admiration for you.
- I will show you a way out of
the palace that will lead us
into open country
beyond the city walls.
We must be very
careful not to be seen.
As soon as night falls, we
can come back to the city.
- [Tom] He looks like a loaf
of split-top bread, doesn't he?
- [Crow] Uh, uh, can
I tell my story now?
I was a big wet hole,
and I battled a...
- [Joel] That's okay, Herc.
♪ Just travelin'
along, singin' a song
♪ Side by side
- [Tom] Come on, sing.
- [Crow] Rip!
- [Joel] Oops.
- [Tom] Looks like
she's in Deep 13.
- [Joel] It's a Heart video!
- [Crow] Round about this time,
the old skunk had gotten
into the pepper pot.
- [Tom] Uh, don't light the
ladder on fire, Conrad Janis.
- [Joel] Yuck, boys!
- The monster's been
killed and the iron bars
are torn apart, but there
isn't any trace of Hercules.
- But no one has ever gotten
out of these caverns alive!
- That man is superhuman,
with such strength
we'll never overpower him.
- [Joel] I quit!
- We will.
But it's necessary
to get him alone,
with none of his friends around.
- What friends?
- I know who they are.
- [Tom] Billy Fasbach.
- Tomorrow I'll arrange
to send away Prince Darix.
- [Crow] Quite a spark
between those two.
- Do you have men you trust
to follow orders implicitly?
- Yes.
- Fine.
- [Tom] Can I borrow a couple?
- Where?
- What does it matter?
- [Joel] Only one thing--
Ow!
- The essential thing is to
keep him from coming back.
And as for Hercules, I
want him taken alive.
He'll pay dearly for what
trouble he's caused me.
- [Crow] Goodnight, punk.
- The queen wouldn't
deny her sister anything.
- [Billis] I know, and
I'm here to ask her
for the greatest
favor of my life.
- Everyone in court
knows the only favor
that will satisfy
the Princess Billis.
- [Joel] Guys, I am
so homesick right now.
- What is it?
- I must talk to you, Samara.
- [Samara] Get out.
- [Crow] Okay, I'll
come back later.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
a Flintstone phone.
- I want you to promise
that you'll hear me out.
- [Tom] I'll hear you out
that door is what I'll do.
- Haven't I always done so?
- [Joel] Marlo
Thomas is That Queen,
- Don't you really
believe I'm fond of you?
- Oh don't say that, Samara.
Even if we didn't
have the same mother,
you've always been a
perfect sister to me.
- [Crow] Rip!
- I want it to be perfectly
clear that my attitude
is dictated solely by
my affection for you.
- Of course.
And because of that
affection, you could make me
the happiest woman in the world.
Samara, Prince Darix loves
me, and if you'll only
give your consent, we'll
be married immediately.
- [Tom] Looks like this
movie's equipped with airbags.
- [Joel] Ooh...
- [Tom] Sorry, sorry.
- Of course not.
How could I refuse you?
- [Crow] No, no, no, no, no!
- Oh Samara, why are
you making us wait?
- It's been my intention
for a long time now
to send Prince Darix
to the court of Corum
to conduct secret negotiations.
- [Tom] Uh, back in
the frame, please.
- Matters of
greatest delicacy...
- [Joel] Toilet paper.
- But he'll be back soon and
you'll live happily ever after.
- [Crow] The end.
- Thank you, dear sister.
- [Tom] Um, leave
the ring please.
- He'll be leaving first
thing tomorrow morning.
While he'll be away from you,
it won't be for very long.
- [Crow] Do-si-do
with an evil queen.
(humming square dance music)
- [Joel] Not for long.
- Claudius is dead,
Hercules has disappeared.
- [Tom] And I'm outta here.
- The two of them were
the only hope we had.
There's nothing left to do.
- You can talk that way because
you don't have children,
but if you had a
daughter like my child,
you'd understand the
anguish that a mother feels
when the moon is
full and you know
they're coming to take
her away to be sacrificed.
- [Joel] It's Lee Meriwether.
(applause)
- My wife is right.
- [Crow] Mickey Rourke!
- You're the only one
who's been to the top of
the Mountain of Death, tell
them what happened to you there.
Speak out, tell us
whether ordinary men
can overcome the monsters.
- I saw the mountain
open up miraculously
and I was bathed in a
blinding green light.
- [Tom] It was great.
- Then huge, deformed
rock-like Moon Mans appeared
and at the same time I was
deafened by a weird sound
that seemed to come from
the depths of the Earth.
After that, I don't
remember anything.
I was so terrified--
- [Crow] I wet 'em.
- I came to after a while
and I found I was alone.
- Your experience
only confirms the fact
that it will not be
easy for us to win.
- T think it's useless.
- [Tom] Harvey Korman!
(applauding)
- All I can say is this.
(blubbering)
- [Tom] Roddy MacDowell, yay!
(applauding)
- I swear to you that
I am not influenced
by any personal ambition.
The only thing I want
is to liberate Samar
from the nightmare
that's afflicting us.
- [Joel] And to direct.
- Then my wife and
I will go away,
asking nothing,
accepting nothing.
- [Crow] Lee Majors,
ladies and gentlemen!
(applause)
- My name is Timor, and
it's on the list of those
who have been selected as the
victims for the sacrifice.
- [Tom] Yeah, boo-hoo.
but I prefer to die in
combat with the monsters
if my death will help
to liberate Samar.
- [Joel] Robert Stack.
(applause)
- Quiet, don't
let them hear you.
- [Tom] Ixnay, shh.
We weren't doing nothing.
It's Clavius, he started it all.
- [Crow] Paul Sorvino!
(applause)
- [Agar] It is I, Agar,
with a friend.
- [Joel] Agarn?
- [Tom] Marlo Thomas,
ladies and gentlemen!
Marlo Thomas!
(applause)
- Welcome, Hercules!
- [Joel] Oh, it's Herc
and he's got the keg!
(cracking)
- With you leading
us, we will win.
- Let me present Prince Darix.
- [Tom] Prince Darix, yay.
- We'll get along well together.
- [Joel] Uh, Herc,
you got hat hair.
- I know of the tragic
destiny that hangs over you
but what would happen if
one day, the people of Samar
were to refuse to send
the sacrificial victims
to the monsters of the mountain?
- [Crow] I think it would
go something like this.
(theme music)
- I never thought
the time would come
when I would great
you with such joy
and in the same breath
have to say goodbye.
- Watch and you'll
see that my horse
will fly on the
wind like Pegasus.
- Take care of yourself,
and come back soon.
When can I hope
to see you again?
- In a few days.
- [Crow] Soon?
- You've spoken of
it to Queen Samara?
- Yes, when she was
giving me the instructions
for the mission I'm to
carry out for her in Corum,
she made several references
to our marriage plans.
- [Tom] Stayczek,
you gettin' this?
- By the way your sister spoke,
it seems she has no objections.
They're sending me
off as her ambassador,
in such good faith.
- Well now you're the most
important relative of the Queen.
- [Joel] Oh ho ho,
you really think so?
- [All] Kiss her, come on!
- [Crow] Why don't you kiss her
instead of talking her to death?
- [Tom] Could you have
a platonic relationship
before Plato?
- [Joel] Hmmm.
Ah, she's all gassed up, sir.
I vacuumed the inside too.
- [Tom] Those are
tegular saddles
with blankets thrown over them!
- [Crow] Have fun
stormin' the castle!
- Is is true that Darix
has been sent away
on orders from the queen?
- Yes.
- [Joel] Slumber party!
- What are you trying to say?
- [Crow] He's toast.
- I don't want to
alarm you, Billis,
but I think it's
necessary you be told.
The queen's aware that Darix is
taking part in the conspiracy.
- But you think he's in danger>
- Yes, I think he's
walking into a trap.
- Oh Agar.
- Come with me, I know a
man who's powerful enough
to help us both, and I'm
sure he won't refuse you.
- [Joel] He's really reasonable
and won't charge for the extras.
- [Tom] Herc's playing
cartoon tag over there.
- [Crow] They're devolving.
- [Tom] Isn't he worried
dirt's gonna stick
to all that oil he's got on him?
- Along that road, they take
the victims to the sacrifice.
Beyond those woods and the
rivers, the Mountain of Death.
- [Tom] Let's buy a pass so
we can go on all the rides.
- [Agar] Hercules!
- [Joel] I thought you were
out of town this weekend!
- [Tom] Zeus is on line
three, you wanna take it?
- They told us at the
tavern you'd be here.
The Princess Billis
needs your help.
- At your service.
- The queen has sent Darix
away on a mission to Corum.
- It's only a pretext,
she found out that Darix
is one of the conspirators.
- Timor, get my horse, fast.
- [Crow] Get my fast horse.
- Darix is already
on the road to Corum?
- Yes, he left
about an hour ago.
- [Joel] Well, oh hi.
- You had better go back
to the palace, Princess.
And don't be afraid.
Even if it costs me my
life, Darix will be saved.
- [Agar] Hercules--
- [Tom] Please don't go
to any trouble for us.
- [Joel] I give
'em three months.
- [Crow] Herc, would
you help us move?
- [Tom] Even if
it costs my life.
- I trust you to get them
safely back to the city.
- [Tom] Even if it
costs you my life.
- [Joel] Yeah, now Herc'll
go to a bar for a few hours
and say he couldn't find him.
(chuckling)
♪ She was calling Wildfire, wild
- [Tom] Ow, ow, ow,
owie, owie, ow, ow, ouch.
- [Crow] Ah, then
Prokofiev showed up!
- [Tom] Hey, whoa!
Sergei, keep it down will ya?
Jiminy.
- [Joel] Hey, there's a lot of
them little guys down there.
- [Joel] Thundering hoofbeats
and a mighty hi-ho Silver.
- [Crow] Not the cliff!
(humming trumpet fanfares)
♪ Hey, it's the Undersea Kingdom
♪ For you and me and it's fun
- [Tom] Whoa, an apple tree!
(yelling)
Oh hi.
- [Crow] Lawrence of Arabia.
- [Tom] Lawrence.
Would you call
this a light trot?
- [Joel] No, it's
really more of a canter
but not quite a gallop.
- [Tom] Trot-ish,
though, I think.
Whoa, whoa.
You should get four-wheel
drive next time, Tom.
- What are you doing?
Ah!
- [Joel] Oh, I see, got it.
- [Tom] Now it's an
Arrow shirt he's wearing.
- [Crow] Just a flesh wound.
- [Tom] Bet that
horse has no name.
- [Joel] Hey, come
back with my arrow!
♪ Marvel the mustang,
he's almost for real
♪ This one's from Hercules,
this one's from Hercules
- [Crow] Just drop me anywhere.
- [Joel] I'm a
Grimwauld warrior!
- [All] Pizza pizza pizza pizza
- [Joel] Stop hurting
him, he's my friend!
Crazy bread, crazy bread!
(blubbering)
- I arrived just in time.
- [Joel] That's a
matter of opinion!
- Don't worry about that.
We've got to think
about your wound.
- [Tom] I can't think
of anything else!
- That arrow's really in deep.
- [Joel] You think so?
- At nightfall, I'll get
you safely into the city.
(grunting)
- [Tom] Ah, please.
Is that a traveling matte?
- [Crow] No, it's a
crappy special effect.
♪ I'm a traveling matte,
I've made a lot of stops
- [Tom] Forgive me Father, for
all I think about is sinning.
- [Joel] Abe Vigoda,
ladies and gentlemen!
(applause)
- Sleeping like a
baby, after that draft
you had prepared for her.
The horses are ready,
no one will see us.
- Let's go.
(rustling)
- Billis!
- [Tom] Schlafly.
- Billis is in danger.
- [Crow] This man
is missing a nipple!
- [Joel] Don't
drip on the carpet.
- Save her.
- [Crow] No, the stain's
not gonna come out.
We're gonna have to
go to the dry cleaner.
- The night of the sacrifice...
- [Joel] Am I
gonna make it, doc?
Will I still be
able to play piano?
- The queen, watch out for her.
- [Joel] The dwarf.
- Leave him to me, Hercules.
I know certain herbs--
- [Tom] Herb Moskowitz,
Herb Edelman, Herb Caen.
- Are you absolutely
sure that he
was attacked on
orders from the queen?
- Yes I am.
They were her soldiers.
What is it that's
turned her against
even her most faithful subjects?
- [Crow] I think she's been
reading the op-ed page.
- And explain why she's
so anxious to get me.
The queen didn't even know me,
she didn't know I
was coming here.
- [Joel] Then she saw
your press pack, Herc.
- And then she nearly caught me.
- [Tom] Oh, he's putting
Crisco on the wound.
- How could she always
guess where I'd be?
- The people say she has
powers that are supernatural.
She possesses a magic
powder which causes any man
who takes it to look at her
through the eyes of love.
They say she's never without it.
She carries it in a gold
locket around her neck.
- [Tom] Well...
- That's useful to
know, when I eventually
come face to face
with Queen Samara.
(laughing)
(peasants yelling)
(theme music)
(grunting)
- Okay, you're all done.
Now, listen, don't
take any food or water
for the next three
hours, alright?
- Okay.
- Wow, Rico-ee
suav-ee over there!
- Why, thank you,
my good fellow.
Say, you're looking rather
Jean-Claude Van Damme yourself!
- Yeah, you really think so?
You know, inside
every Servo is an
Alan Steel waiting to get out.
Okay, okay, Joel, ask me
"Which way to the beach?"
- Oh, just hold it a
second, my beefy bots.
You need one more accessory to
really augment your ensemble.
- Huh, what, say what?
- Yeah, you need a
new name that's as
big and brawny as your
new upper-body implants.
- Oh, right!
Well, what good is a tough
guy without a tough-guy name?
- Yeah, exactly.
You know, the general rule
of thumb is that you take a,
have a real virile first name,
like Alan, and then a second
name that sounds like some kind
of hard surface, like Steel.
Alan Steel, get it?
- Oh, I get it!
Okay, my new name
is Drake Tungsten.
- Good!
- And you have to
call me that too.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay,
I dub me Russ Tile Floor.
(chuckling and growling)
- Well, uh, I don't know
if that really works,
'cause that makes your middle
name Tile and you'd have to
put it in quotation marks
or parentheses or something.
- Oh.
- And then that would
make your last name Floor,
which really isn't
all that great.
- Okay, okay, how about this?
Ric, R-I-C, Drywall,
Ric Drywall!
- Well, drywall
really isn't that...
I mean, it's not like, you know,
concrete or something hard.
- Yeah, Crow's right.
- Drake.
- Drake's right.
- Okay, fine! Fine!
- Hey Tom, how about
Adam Plexiglass?
- Yeah, or, uh, Vic Kevlar?
- Nick Pig-Iron.
- Look, just forget it, okay?
- Jim J. Bullock!
- Now that's not funny!
Just drop the whole thing!
Just drop it now, okay?
- Well listen, maybe you
could be one of those
tough guys without
a tough-guy name,
like Sylvester
Stallone or something.
- Oh, don't patronize me, Joel.
- Oh, uh, Tom, I
hate to tell you,
but you just rejected
your donor limbs.
- I knows that. don't
you think I know that?!
I'm living it, I know
it, I'm here living it!
(sobbing)
- Hey, Servo, I just thought
of a good name for you.
- Really, what?
- Danny No-Arms!
- Lemme at him!
(yelling and alarms blaring)
- Oh, we got movie sign!
- [Crow] Freddy Fireplug.
- [Tom] Shut up, Crow.
- [Crow] Tommy Torso.
- [Tom] Thanks for giving
me my arms back, Joel.
- Hercules, they're here!
- {guard[ You in
there, can you Hear Me?
- [Joel] I'll move the
dead guy, you get the door.
- Open.
- [Tom] Sesame.
- [Woman] My daughter...
- [Joel] Your daughter what?
- Take her, go on, go on.
- [Joel] Bake-o?
(loud knocking)
- [Crow] Who is it,
I'm doing the dishes.
Cheeser, cheeser.
- We're here to
take your daughter.
Where is she?
- No!
- [Tom] I think she's
over there somewhere.
(yelling)
- [Crow] Alright, help yourself.
- [Joel] Okay but you have
to have her home by 11!
- Let go, let go!
- [Tom] Watch me rock!
- [Tom] Ooh, good thing
they made everything
out of balsa wood
back then, huh?
- [Crow] Ooh,
right in the store!
- [Joel] Owie.
- [Tom] It's a barrel of fun!
(goofy laughing)
- [Joel] A barrel of Hun.
- [Joel] Gilligan, no!
- [Tom] Gilligan, yes.
Behold the only thing
greater than yourself!
- [Joel] Now there's
two guys in there!
Hi-keeba!
- [Tom] Oh, batter up.
- [Joel] Gymkata, Doc Marten.
- [Crow] Gymkata!
- [Tom] Oh neat, a flamer.
(humming goofy sitcom music)
- [Joel] I love my job.
Pizza pizza this!
- Hercules.
- [Tom] Here.
- There's no time to be wasted,
they'll be returning
with reinforcements.
You must find a safe
place for Darix.
- I know a place
where he can hide.
- [Joel] That one
was just for me.
- [Crow] Someday
that's gonna be a mall.
- Hercules!
- [Tom] Oh, that's me.
Here, hold this guy, will ya?
- [Joel] Listen, I
know I said I'd call
but I was attacked
by guards and then--
- Billis has been taken.
I saw her in chains with
the other prisoners.
- Go on ahead!
They're on the march?
- Yes, but don't go now.
You can't do anything alone,
I beg you wait for the others.
- No, that might be too late.
- What would become of me if
anything should happen to you?
- Don't worry.
- [Crow] There are other
demigods out there.
- [Joel] Hello
Laverne, hi Shirl.
(humming along with soundtrack)
- [Crow] On your left!
- [Tom] Looks like they
bagged their limit today, huh?
- [Crow] I guess what they
say about lemmings isn't true.
Really forced busing.
♪ Chain chain chain,
chain of fools
- [Tom] You know,
it's never as fun
as it looks in the brochures.
- [Joel] I hate
these cattle calls.
- [Crow] Ugh, looks like
somebody got beer on the film.
- [Joel] So I said, why don't
you try pushing the rope?
Okay, I'll be the
slave, I'm sorry.
- [Tom] Isn't this a drag folks?
(groaning)
Little pun there
for the chain gang.
- [Crow] Hey I'm not
enjoying this, it's my job.
- [Joel] Tri-Star--
Oh, try it again.
Tri-Star Pictures,
there, good one.
- [Tom] Okay, sit, stay,
that's a good horse!
Oh, such a good horse, oh yes!
- [Crow] I coulda gone my
whole life without seeing that.
♪ Little Jeannie
(humming)
♪ Wanna dance with somebody
- [Joel] Uh Herc,
they're all dead.
- [Crow] Oh come on, you've
been resisting for 300 miles!
Now come on!
- [Joel] We're planning to move
the sacrifice area
closer to the city.
- [Tom] Those tour routes are
rather harsh, aren't they?
- [Joel] I'm starting to
feel like Bob Mantell.
- [Crow] Boing, boing,
boing, boing, boing.
- [Joel] Man, I'm stuck
jelly-tight in this thing.
- Here they come.
- [All] Surprise!
(coughing)
- [Tom] Well, they're
dragging them along, eh?
- [Crow] Hey, these guys
are gettin' harder to pull.
- [Joel] The bad news is the
chief wants to water-ski!
(goofy chuckling)
(crunching)
- [Tom] Come here.
- [Joel] Leave him
alone, you big bullies!
- Come, Princess.
But you're not Billis!
- [Joel] Well you're
not Steve Reeves!
- [Tom] Oh no, it's a giant
Joe Namath netted
slingshot brief!
- [Crow] Oh wait,
he can bend steel
but he can't break
through a net!?
- We've got you at last.
- [Tom] Uh, Hercules.
- [Joel] Next week on
Hercules versus the Moon Men.
- [Tom] Please do not
touch the exhibit.
- [Crow] It's Kim Catrell!
- [Joel] No...
There is nothing wrong
with your television set.
- [Tom] And there's
Marcia Brady!
- [Joel] No it's not.
- [Crow] I'm next
for the mud bath.
- [Moon Man] You see...
- [Joel] Oh not this guy
again, I was having a moment!
- They're absolutely identical.
- That is why I ordered
you to bring your princess.
- [Tom] Looks like the
Great Root Bear, doesn't it?
Soon Selena will awaken
from her long sleep
and will live again through
the blood of Billis.
- [All] Eww!
- You're my own sister, you
brought me here to kill me!
How could you be such a monster?
- [Crow] Oh come on, we've
never been that close.
- Say it isn't true, Samara!
- [Tom] Look into your heart!
- Samara, Samara!
♪ I love ya, Samara
- No!
- [Joel] Hi-keeba!
Whoa, its the
Monsters of Rock tour!
(screaming)
- [Tom] Wanna get stoned?
♪ Everybody must get stoned
- [Joel] It's the inhumanoids!
- [Tom] Sorry you had
to see that there.
- The sacrifice will take
place tomorrow night.
- [Crow] Please
bring a dish to pass.
- When the planet Saturn comes
into conjunction with Mars,
and under the evil
influence of Uranus.
- Oh, you mean it's Tuesday.
- Then will occur
unimaginable disaster.
The oceans will rise,
the mountains crumble
and inexorably our moon
will draw near the Earth.
- [Joel] Oh, they would
have done that anyway.
- Through this cataclysm, only
our form of life can survive.
After the long night--
- [Crow] I can
see his lips move.
- We shall become the
masters of the Earth.
- [Joel] Does that make me
Mrs. Master of the Earth?
- But how shall I live, then?
- [Crow] Uh, I'll
check the manual.
- You will have the
reward you have earned.
- [Tom] It's a new car!
- Your beauty will never fade,
and your power will
be equal to ours.
You will possess all
the riches of the world.
But remember that there is still
one task you must carry out.
Kill Hercules.
- Have no fear.
- [Joel] Underdog is here!
- He will die.
(creaking)
- [Tom] I do this all the
time, it doesn't hurt at all.
- [Crow] Hi Hercules,
aren't you gonna wave to me?
- [Joel] Oh hi--
Argh!
- [Tom] Don't wave.
- [Crow] Good thing they
left space for his hands.
Come on, oh...
Ah, there ya go, that's the way.
- [Tom] It's still
fun, I'm still smilin'.
- [All] Dang me, dang me,
take a rope and hang me...
- [Tom] Come on, sing!
- [Joel] Break time!
[Crow] Gregory Pecs.
- [Tom] Oh, so the spikes are
gonna stab him if he lets go!
I just got it, oh...
- [Joel] Oh, nipple cam.
- [Tom] Bonnie Rait!
(gobbling)
She's a survivor, you know.
- [Crow] So, he's really strong?
(creak)
- [Tom] A piercing problem.
Will Hercules escape?
Tune in next week, same Herc
time, same Herc channel.
- [Joel] Uh, could
somebody scratch my nose?
- [All] Trailers
for sale or rent.
Rooms to let...
(groaning)
- [Crow] Bet those
things are hard to clean.
- [Tom] Actually
no, they fold down
and there's a nice
convenient brush.
- [Joel] You know, the
machine doesn't see Hercules
the way you or I do, the
machine sees Hercules
as a series of ones and zeros.
- [Tom] I was wondering.
- [Crow] Boy, it's
getting close.
- [Tom] It's
indicating his pecs.
- [Joel] Bronzer, check it out.
- [Tom] Oh yes, oh yes...
- [Joel] Please, please, God,
if you get me out of this
I promise I'll do anything
you want, I promise.
- [Tom] Tie me kangaroo down...
You know, if you squint
real hard it looks like
he's being stuck with several
Transamerica buildings.
- [Joel] Headache tension!
I'm sending you
good vibes, Herc!
I am.
- [Tom] Hey, I'm gaining on 'em!
- [All] Whee!
- Stop!
- [Joel] In the name of love!
- [Crow] So, lunch?
- Conduct him to my quarters.
(humming sultry music)
- [Tom] Oh look, a Smokey Joe.
- [Joel] Very funny, guys.
- All of you go.
- [Crow] But why are
you laying like th--
Oh.
- [Tom] Cheap cuffs.
Here, let me just, ah.
- A hundred lances
pointed at your heart.
Just one little gesture from me
and you would have
been lying at my feet.
- [Joel] Well I could
still lie at your feet
if you want me to.
- But I prefer the
challenge you offer alive.
(howling and gibbering)
♪ I'm Hans Christian Anderson
- Why all you'd have to
do is reach out a hand.
(crunching)
- [Crow] Ow, just kidding.
- You'd break my neck the way
you break the stem of a flower.
- [Joel] You are
one spooky chick.
- Why don't you do it?
- You have nothing
to fear from me.
- [Crow] But fear itself.
- Now that I've seen you, I can
no longer rebel against you.
I want to stay with you.
It's Hercules who asks this.
No slave is as
faithful as I would be.
- [Crow] It's daddy,
come on, me, Herc.
- [Tom] Let me close
the drapes here...
- [Joel] I am always getting
into these situations.
Call it life of Riley.
(imitating alarm blaring)
- [Tom] Plot point, plot
point, plot point, plot point.
- Come Hercules, come and
drink to our friendship.
- [Tom] Hmm, now you would
assume that I would think
that the poison was in this cup.
- We'll toast our union, the
strongest force in the qorld.
- [Crow] I want
the Garfield cup.
- But you'll never
be sorry that you've
taken your place at my side.
- [Joel] Mmm, his
lips are strong too.
- [Guard] My queen!
- Get out!
- [Guard] I'm sorry,
Majesty, but it's urgent.
- Wait outside.
- [All] Argh!
- [Crow] Oh no, are we gonna
find her irresistible now?
- [Joel] Oh, Herc's been
working with Uta Hagen, I guess.
- [Crow] Herc very
sleepy, must get shut-eye.
- [Tom] I'm so sleepy I
can barely keep awake.
- [Joel] Hmm, now I think
I'll dress him up a bit.
- [Tom] Well, who's
not on my list?
- Darix is alive.
- [Tom] And well,
and living in Paris.
- He was rescued by
Hercules, who fell upon us
and massacred the entire escort.
- Where's Darix now?
- I don't know, my queen.
I was badly wounded, but I
managed to drag myself here.
- To tell me you
failed in your mission?
Execute him.
- [Guard] No, no, no!
- Darix free means
trouble for us.
We must capture him.
- That's not difficult.
All we have to do
is follow Agar.
- [Crow] And follow our bliss.
(humming sultry music)
- [Joel] Ah yes, the buffet.
- You throught you could trick
Samara, but I'm too clever.
(imitating snoring)
- Once you wake up, you'll
be my most faithful slave.
- [Joel] You know,
all these movies
revolve around Herc sleeping.
- [Crow] That's 'cause he
can remember how to do it.
- [Tom] Why is he laying
on a big cupcake wrapper?
- [Joel] He's cream-filled.
- [Crow] Herc, you scamp!
(chuckling)
- [Joel] You know,
I've been to paradise
but I've never been to me.
Nice digs.
- [Tom] Fluff
these up, sit back,
just wait for the
chicks to roll in.
- [Joel] Life of Riley,
yep, life of Riley.
(theme music)
- [Samara] You dare to
conspire against me.
You've helped our enemies,
and you've fallen in
love with Hercules.
- [Crow] Good job, McCloud.
- I ought to punish you
with death for this,
but too much blood
has already been shed.
And now that Hercules
is in my power,
you no longer represent
any danger to us.
(gobbling)
I banish you from Samar.
Leave my kingdom forever!
- [Joel] You're fired,
clean out your dress!
(crying)
- [Crow] Way to banish her.
You're good.
♪ It's the shiny little heinie
with the fringe on the top
- No, you mustn't.
Your wound hasn't healed,
and where would you go?
The minute you go outside,
they'll capture you.
- Timor, you've already
taken great risks
and I'm very grateful.
- [Joel] Iron my
pants, will you?
- But I cannot wait any longer.
- [Tom] Oh please, here.
Put your top on,
you'll feel better.
- Billis has
completely disappeared.
Hercules is in the dungeons
and there's no news from Agar.
- [Joel] There, doesn't
that make it nice?
- In the hands of the queen.
- [Joel] Oh, who hasn't been
in the hands of the queen?
- And I must talk to our friend.
- [Crow] Now cough.
- See how week you are?
I'll go myself, just
tell me what to say.
(knocking)
- [Agar] Timor,
it's Agar, open up!
- [Tom] Ah, lousy
Jehovah;s Witnesses.
Here, wait a minute,
I'll get rid of 'em.
Uh hi, look we just
sat down to breakfast--
Oh.
- Agar, we thought you were--
- Yes, but I was
sent into exile.
We must try to save Hercules.
- And Billis?
- She wasn't among
the other victims.
- Where is she?
_ I don't know.
Hercules was trying to find her.
(banging)
- [Crow] L.A.P.D!
(humming Star Trek fight music)
- [Tom] This 926 Maple?
Oh geez, I got the
wrong address, sorry.
- [Joel] Meanwhile
in Hef's grotto.
♪ Come here young children
and bring me your wine
♪ Oh bitter dregs
- Send them away.
(clapping)
- [Crow] Now bring them back.
I love it when you do that.
[Joel] Is that a polar bear rug?
- [Tom] Uh, no, it's his horse!
- Because I wanted
to be alone with you.
- [Tom] Because I want to know
what makes you,
Queen Samara, tick.
(kissing)
- [Joel] Hey, you taste
like Steve Reeves.
- Samara, you told me
many marvelous things.
- [Tom] You told me
a fabricated story
that wouldn't convince a child!
- You said that at your
side, I would become
the most powerful
man in the world.
- [Tom] Nice pose.
- [Tom] You never explained how
these things would come to pass.
- [Joel] Hey Herc, James
Brolin wants his beard back.
- After tonight,
you'll know the answer.
- I don't understand how in
the space of a few hours,
you can change our destiny.
What could happen of
such great importance?
- You must have faith in me.
Tonight you'll be at my
side and you'll know.
You'll be able to see
with your own eyes
that I've told you the truth.
- [Crow] I saw it with my own
eyes, what a dumb expression.
- The important thing now is
that you tell me you love me.
- [Joel] On our
first date, ouch.
- I love you, Samara.
- And you've never loved
anyone else as much?
- [Tom] Well I had
a dog once, but...
- [Crow] You think I
wear too much makeup?
(rustling)
(gong ringing)
- [Joel] Oh, Jaye P.
Morgan gonged her.
- [Crow] My blankie.
- You know them?
- Yes, they were the ones who
tried to set me against you.
- [Samara] And she,
wasn't she your friend?
- Friend?
She's just a girl that
took me in like the others.
- How can you betray us?
- I told you that you
were completely in
my power, didn't I?
And I also ordered you
to get out of my kingdom.
- [Joel] And Isaac Hayes
wants his vest back!
- [Samara] What sentence
shall I decree for them?
- [Crow] Hmm, something crunchy.
- The death penalty.
- [Joel] All around,
on the house!
- A slow death.
Let them die of starvation,
give them plenty of time
to regret having taken
up arms against you.
- This isn't you,
it's not possible.
- [Samara] He's right.
Take them away and see that
the orders are carried out.
- [Tom] Right, two
slow deaths coming up.
- [Crow] Hey Bob, we
need two slow deaths!
Wreck 'em.
- [Joel] Snaggletooth, eee.
- Listen to me.
I understand your doubts
because I share them.
Did you think I was
naturally a warlike spirit?
- [Crow] Well, yes.
- I'm only a tavern keeper,
but also I know that
this is the moment for
us to stand up like men
or we'll never know what
it is to be free men again.
- What do you expect us to do?
They know who we
are and soon they'll
be coming here to arrest us.
Timor's been killed, Darix
is in the hands of the queen
and we don't even know
whether Hercules is alive.
- Hercules isn't a
man to let himself
be put out of the
way that easily.
- I agree with Tertius.
I have a son.
- [Tom] Howard Johnson's right!
- That doesn't change anything.
- [Man] Let me in, I say!
- [Peasant] Orders are orders.
- You can let him in, Raynon.
- [Joel] Chong.
- An officer of the royal guard.
- [Tom] Can we get
some service here?
- Rubio, what are
you doing here?
- I know just what you
and your companions
are plotting to do and it would
have been very easy for me
to have taken you by surprise
and have you put to death.
- [Tom] It's John Delorean, yay!
- The army is with me,
we must fight together.
(many people talking at once)
- You have sworn
a military oath?
- No man of honor can be
tied by an oath that requires
that he cover
himself with shame.
(imitating growling speech)
What's more, my soldiers are
men of the people like you.
(imitating growling speech)
- He's right.
Come on men, let's
storm the palace!
- [Crow] Killing's okay, yay!
- Come here Hercules,
look at that.
- [Joel] A ceiling fan?
- [Joel] Oh come on, let's love.
- [Samara] It's from the
moon that my power will come.
- From the moon?
What do you mean?
(squeaking)
- now that I'm really sure
you're mine, I
needed to tell you.
- [Joel] You're greasy.
- For many years, my
ancestors were sorcerers
to the monsters of the mountain,
but I've gone even further.
I'm their ally.
- [Tom] Geez, and
I made love to you?
- Allied with death?
- Yes.
They are powerful, Hercules
but despite their power,
without me they're helpless.
- What help could you give?
- [Tom] 401k, health
plan, the usual.
- I gave them Billis.
- [Crow] Yikes, I can just
imagine what you're giving me!
- Her sacrifice will
revive Selena, their queen.
- Where is Billis?
- In the Mountain of Death.
- Perfect, that's exactly
what I wanted to find out.
- What are you saying!?
- You thought you had
me under your spell,
but your magic philter
didn't work on me.
I know what I was
doing all the time,
and now I must liberate
Darix and Agar.
- [Tom] Ah, she's got
one of those, huh?
I hate that.
- [Crow] Ah crap,
I sang like a bird.
- [Joel] Grab the gusto
of life, Herc's way!
- [Tom] Now, back
to what I love.
This is what I was built for,
not figuring out
secret passages.
Good old-fashioned violence.
Back in town.
- [Crow] Me next, me
next, twirl me, twirl me!
- [Joel] Pizza pizza, my ass.
You've been gonged!
(laughs)
- [Tom] Now this, this
is what I'm good at.
Let's face it, this
is my strong suit.
I'm no Rhodes scholar but I have
a real knack for
this sort of thing.
I'm glad I chose kicking
butt as a career.
Now back to some fun, huh?
Come on, join me.
There we go.
Let's dance.
- [Joel] He's
doing the haymaker!
(screaming)
- [Crow] I guess you
won't be needing that!
- [Guard] He's going
into the dungeon!
- [Joel] Sorry you can't get in
without a backstage pass, ha ha!
- [Crow] Uh, do you
have a bobby pin?
- [Tom] Wilma!
- [Darix] I knew you
weren't a traitor.
- [Tom] Let's roll.
- Hurry.
- He musn't get out
of the palace alive!
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Joel, I hate
movies where the men
wear shorter skirts
than the women.
- Boy, don't you know it.
I can just imagine a scene from
the days of Ancient Greece.
Oh, hi, Hercules, have a seat--
Noooo no no!
- You are so right,
little itty buddy.
Hey Cambot, cue up the music.
That's why we've put together
a little musical presentation
honoring one of our
favorite garments.
It's a little thing
we like to call Pants!
♪ Pants
♪ Sing the praises of pants
♪ Nothing better shows my taste
♪ Than what I wear
below my waist
♪ Say, pants
♪ Pants
♪ Sing the praises of pants
♪ They help me suck in my gut
♪ They always cover up my butt
♪ Pants
♪ Sing the praises of pants
♪ Wear them and
you're a cool guy
♪ As long as you zip up your fly
♪ Zip
♪ Pants
♪ Sing the praises of pants
- That's right ladies and
gentlemen, consider the pant!
You know, the Pant
Association urges you
to wear your pants at
least three times a day!
- The great men of our
time have all worn pants.
Roosevelt, Churchill,
DeGualle, Ghandi!
Well, almost all of them!
- Dolphins, one of the
smartest mammals on Earth.
Do they wear pants?
No, but they wish they did!
That's how smart they are!
- What keeps our legs
all warm and hot?
- [Both] Pants!
- What prevents a buffalo shot?
- What do they got
that I ain't got?
- [Both] Pants!
- Oh, you can say that again.
Huh?
♪ Pants
♪ Yang dang dang dang da Pants
♪ Dang'a dang dang
(nervous chuckling)
Deep hurting!
- Go ahead and sing, pantywaist.
In a moment, you're going
to be knee-deep in sand
and then itíll be
Joel Robinson, R.I.P.!
- Rest In Pants?
(sneezing)
- [Crow] You're locking
it from this side!
I'll open it in a minute, geez!
- [Tom] Call him Stanley,
the garage door opener.
Whoa.
- [Joel] How about a
little fire, Scarecrow?
- [Crow] Oh come on,
you're only making it
worse for yourself,
I'm Hercules!
- [Tom] My name
is Inigo Montoya.
You killed my father,
prepare to die.
- [Crow] You die, Joe.
- [Tom] Ah geez,
that was really dumb.
What was I thinking?
- [Joel] Good one, Hercu-loser.
This is wild, I've never
killed a guy like this before.
Neat!
- [Tom] Oh, they want an encore.
- [Joel] Oh, it's the
open auditions for
Torch Song Trilogy.
- Hercules is already
on the way, let's go!
- [Tom] Well guys,
this movie's pretty bad
but it's nothing
we can't handle.
- [Crow] Yeah, I don't
know what that whole
deep hurting stuff was about.
- [Tom] Oh no!
- [Crow] Oh!
- [Tom] It's a sandstorm scene!
(crying)
- [Joel] It's okay, be cool,
it's just another scene.
Let's just riff like normal,
nothing to worry about.
I'll lead.
- [Tom] Dorothy, Dorothy!
How's that?
- [Joel] Good.
- [Crow] It was
after the apocalypse,
they had to get to
the power station.
They weren't prepared
for the robot holocaust.
- [Tom] Arakis,
Dune, desert planet.
- [Joel] Oh boy, she could
really use a Dustbuster!
(laughing)
- [Tom] Looks like
downtown St. Paul
after 5:00 in the afternoon!
- [Joel] She's wearing Hair-Epox
because it's wind tunnel tested!
♪ Everyone knows it's windy
- [Joel] This is kinda like
seeing bad performance art.
- [Tom] Like seeing performance
art, in other words.
- [Joel] Ooh, stingy.
- [Tom] Oh, so what's
the Pope doing here?
- Redolphis, Redolphis!
- [Joel] Red Rover, Red
Rover, let moon men come over!
- Redolphis, save me.
In a moment, Hercules
will be here.
- You betrayed us.
- [Crow] UB-40.
- [Tom] Eubie Blake.
- [Joel] It's clobberin' time.
- [Samara] No!
No, don't kill me,
I didn't betray you.
I'm the one who was betrayed!
No, no!
♪ We will, we will rock you
- Help, save me, no!
No!
- [Crow] It's
Stonehenge on Ice!ú
- Save me!
Redolphis, stop them, no!
- [Joel] Oh no, not the
Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robots!
They're gonna
knock my block off!
(screaming)
- [Crow] How humiliating,
she's being killed by a patio.
- [Tom] Those things are great
'cause you can
hose 'em right off.
- [Crow] Oh, Joel,
I'm getting nervous
about this sandstorm thing.
- [Joel] Don't
worry, little buddy.
Just keep the quips
coming, we'll be okay.
- [Tom] Oh, this is like
a bad Antonioni movie.
- [Crow] Like an Antonioni
movie, in other words.
- [Tom] Baboom.
- [Joel] Oh geez, I wish
I had my shirt on now.
My nips are burning!
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells
- [Tom] Oh, pardon me.
- Selena, Selena.
- [Tom] Come on, get up,
we're going to Grandma's now.
- Your hour has come.
- [Crow] I've got to go lend
my outfit to Iman
or David Bowie.
- [Joel] Eww, he's cutting
her with a pizza knife!
- [Crow] Pizza pizza.
- [Joel] Alvin!
- [Crow] Chicago style.
Eww, I hate that part of my job.
- [Tom] What?
Ah cripes, I should really
get that leak fixed up there.
- [Joel] Well, the
Jiffy Pop's done.
- [Tom] And I don't care.
- [Joel] Oh wow.
- [Moon Man] Drop
by drop, this blood
will bring you back
to life, my queen.
- [Tom] Oh, she's
packed in excelsior.
- [Darix] Follow me!
- [Crow] Oh Joel,
it's a sandstorm.
- [Tom] Sandstorm, guys.
- [Joel] Sandstorm.
- [Tom] Yep.
- [Joel] Couldn't
just one person
have gone and reported back?
- [Tom] This is
what they get for
going to Kansas during
tornado season, huh?
- [Darix] Come on, everybody.
- [Joel] And do the
Locomotion with me!
- [Tom] But the Berenstain Bears
could find nowhere
to picnic, so...
(indistinct shouting)
- [Crow] Quick before
the film starts again!
- [Man] Come on, keep moving!
- [Tom] Hey, we're
losing all the topsoil!
- [Joel] There goes Nebraska!
- [Crow] I tell ya, when Herc
breaks wind everybody suffers!
- [Joel] We should have
checked the Weather channel!
- [Tom] Well, this is
really killing time.
I figure we could do three
or four more minutes,
what do you think?
- [Crow] I'm an
ax-wielding maniac!
- [Tom] And he's dancing
like he never danced before!
Hey, moon over Parador there.
- [Crow] So this
is Chicago, huh?
Oh, oh shoot, I lost my contact.
Everybody stop where
you are, don't step!
(crunching)
- [Joel] Somebody's having
their blood pressure checked.
- [Crow] It's icky.
(liquid trickling)
- [Tom] Louise Brooks
(eerie electrical humming)
- [Joel] I think there's
a short in the fan.
- [Crow] Welcome to the crypt!
I've got a bone
to pick with you.
(cackling)
- [Tom] Shut up.
- [Joel] Kinda like a
freaked out Viewmaster.
(wind howling)
- [Crow] We now return
to Endless Summer.
- [Tom] I think I'll just
break this for the heck of it,
there we go.
- [Crow] I lost my retainer!
- [Joel] Oh, this is like
an Outward Bound weekend
gone horribly wrong.
- [Tom] I'll say.
Well, this is what they
get for trying to shortcut.
- [Joel] These are the outtakes
from Here to Eternity, I think.
- [Tom] No Joel, this
is just eternity.
- [Crow] Like True Grit.
Imagine what it would be like
if something were happening.
- [Tom] All the hair's been
blasted off Herc's chest there.
- [Joel] Okay, that's enough,
we've had it with the
sandstorm sequence!
- [Tom] Easy, Joel.
Oh for crying, they're up
around the same set again!
(sighing)
- [Crow] You know, the Mads
said this was gonna be bad,
and you know what?
They're right!
(Tom and Crow yelling)
(all crying)
- [Tom] Buck up.
- [Joel] Hey, none of us
can go on any further!
- [Tom] We'll meet you
there, we'll get a table.
We'll order you a sandwich!
(chuckling)
(crying)
Please end this scene,
please oh please oh please...
- [Joel] It's okay, buddy.
Let it out, let it
out, that's good.
- [Crow] We got
problems too, lady!
- [Tom] Help the bombardier!
- [Crow] I am the bombardier!
- [Tom] Well then help him.
- [Joel] Guys I think I'm
giving in to deep hurting...
- [Crow] , no, no no,
Joel, I've got an idea.
Let's sing a song okay?
♪ Row, row, row your boat
♪ Gently down the stream
♪ Merrily, merrily,
merrily, merrily
Come on, sing!
- [Tom] I don't want to!
- [Crow] Come on, sing!
(theme music)
I said sing, dammit, sing!
♪ Row, row, row your boat
♪ Gently down the stream
(crying)
- [Joel] Come on you
guys, knock it off!
Come one, we can make if
if we can resume riffing.
Come on.
- [Tom] I never should have
gone to the Sands hotel!
- [Joel] Good, good,
keep it coming.
- [Crow] There's gonna
be rock climbing, no!
(all yelling)
- [Tom] Herc, don't bend
over, don't bend over.
Please don't.
- [Joel] Thanks for
turning around, Herc.
You're a real gentleman,
appreciate it.
- [Tom] Oh, we're
gonna make it, guys.
- [Crow] Oh yeah,
oh, that's the spot.
That feels good.
- [Tom] This is taking kind of a
Herculean effort
for him isn't it?
- [Joel] Boy, I
shouldn't have ever
taken that week
off from the gym.
- [Tom] The burning,
the itching.
Try Curex.
Cool, it's a Dali painting.
- [Crow] I could
watch that all day.
- [Joel] Here comes
someone who can help you.
- [Crow] Why is he
wearing oven mitts?
♪ See you on the
dull side of the moon
- [Crow] Plop plop, fizz fizz.
♪ Mr. Yuk is green
- [Tom] I'd say a
little more blush
and a little less
bronzer for her.
The fall look.
- [Crow] Meanwhile,
two hours later.
(coughing)
(all yelling)
- [Crow] This is like the
planet of 98-pound weaklings.
Everyone gets sand
kicked in their face!
- Perhaps we'll find him
on the Mountain of Death.
Come on!
- [Tom] Come on,
even though he's gone
we can still make
this movie dull!
Come on, he would have
wanted it that way!
Who are they talking about?
- [Joel] I think
they should just
call the school
picnic off, don't you?
- [Crow] This is your brain
on drugs, any questions?
- [Tom] Well, as a
matter of fact...
♪ Let's go surfin' now,
everybody's learnin' how
- [Joel] Hey, I was looking
for the ultimate wave
and I found it on Death
Mountain, perfect wave.
(humming eerie music)
- [Tom] Wow, steamin'
mad at this movie.
♪ The weather
started getting rough
♪ The tiny ship was
- [Tom] At least it isn't
a sandstorm anymore.
- [Crow] Oh, I've seen dogs
do that on the driveway.
- [Tom] Oh, I should
have brought my totes.
- [Joel] Oh my goodness,
it's the great urinal cake!
(sniffing)
- [Crow] Lime.
- [Tom] Dianetics,
by L. Ron Hubbard.
- [Joel] Why do I
hurt inside, page 54.
- [Tom] When will this
stupid movie end, page 38?
- [Crow] How much money can we
get out of Tom Cruise, page 25.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Neat.
- [Joel] Ah I told you you'd
come crawling back to the Herc.
- [Crow] The world is
having a Maalox moment.
- [Joel] I guess so.
- [Tom] Well, I gotta hand
it to those mad scientists.
This is one of the
worst sequences
in one of the worst
movies we've ever seen.
- [Joel] Just set
myself anywhere.
- [Tom] Oh, this is
like the scene in Dune,
you know, when the Imperial
saucer comes crashing down
and Paul and Jessica are
stranded, and Jessica says...
(speaking quickly)
Never mind.
- [Crow] It's a woman in a dune.
- [Tom] It's a
cowgirl in the sand.
- [Joel] I'm gonna make a
castle, that's what I'll do.
- [Tom] Oh, brother.
Really long pointless
scene back there.
- [All] Yay!
(applause)
- [Joel] Finally.
- [Tom] Alright.
Get a piece of this rock.
- [Crow] Heh heh, sticks
and stones, ha ha ha.
- [Joel] Right in the
stones, I like that.
- [Tom] Kinda like
he's trapped in a
giant Foosball table isn't it?
- [Crow] Gumby, no!
- [Tom] How about a Martini
and Rossi on the rocks?
Heh heh, I'm funny.
Really cute, huh?
♪ Here we come,
walkin' down the street
- [Crow] Is that his butt?
- [Tom] Huh, neat.
Hey, I'm thinking,
I'm actually thinking!
- [Joel] Hey, she's
lying in Gainesburger.
- [Moon Man] Stop him, kill him!
- [Crow] In that order?
- [Tom] You guys
are rock stupid.
I slay me.
- [Crow] Whatever
you do, don't let him
pick you up over his head!
- [Tom] It all looks so good,
I don't know where to start.
- [Joel] Aaah, gymkata!
- [Tom] Don't make me laugh,
Woodsey Owl, get outta here.
- [Crow] My name is Hercules
and I'm a rock-aholic!
- [Joel] Hi, Herc.
Help me, Great Root Bear!
- [Tom] It's like they're being
attacked by Mont Saint-Michel.
- [Joel] Uh, could you
hold up a minute, guys?
I'll be with you in a second.
- [Crow] I'm still awake.
- [Tom] Yeah, I am too,
whatcha thinkin' about?
- [Crow] Hey, that's obscene!
- [Joel] Oh, why...
- [Tom] Ladies and
gentlemen, Stonehenge!
- [Joel] This film has aged me.
- [Crow] I know how she feels.
♪ It sure isn't you
- [Tom] Backdraft.
- [Joel] Epilogue.
(whistling and bird calls)
- [Tom] Springtime in Washington
D.C. means cherry blossoms.
- [Crow] Glad that's over.
- Do you really have
to leave us, Hercules?
- Yes, Prince.
I' may be needed in some
other parts of the world.
- [Joel] You know how it
is, being the Herc and all.
- Billis and I hoped that Agar
could persuade you to stay.
- [Hercules] Can I persuade Agar
to share the risks I
will surely encounter?
- [Joel] Touche.
- For the rest of my life.
- [Tom] But they're not married.
Oh...
- [Crow] Geez, her
dress is filthy.
- [Tom] Gonna get
uncomfortable up there.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
- [Joel] Hercules will be
back in Herc Goes Bananas.
- [Tom] Oh, I hope not.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- You know Joel, it bothers me
when they switch actors on us.
Hercules Unchained had
Steve Reeves and now
Hercules Against the Moon Men
has Alan Steel, what happened?
- I know, you have to kinda
squint and tilt your head
a little to make Alan Steel
look like Steve Reeves.
- Steve's more shiny.
- Right, that's exactly right.
Well, actually it happens
quite often, you know,
the movie industry is so
bloated and sluggish it takes
years for a sequel to even
a popular movie to get made.
- Ouch.
- Yeah, and what happened
was Steve Reeves did so well
in Hercules Unchained he
probably came back to the studio
asking for a lot more money,
they couldn't meet his price,
enter Alan Steel.
- Yeah, we call that the
Wayne Rogers Syndrome.
- The Wayne Rogers huh?
- Yeah, exactly.
It's an old adage in Hollywood,
when you're doing a remake
of a movie for television
and you can't get
the film actor to do it,
you call Wayne Rogers.
- Oh, you mean like when
he replaced Elliot Gould
for the TV version of M.A.S.H.?
- Exactly.
- Or when he replaced Donna Reed
in the TV version of
It's A Wonderful Life.
- Oh yeah--
Buh?
- It's complicated,
when you're older.
- Oh don't forget him
trying to erase the memory
of Walter Matthau in the
TV remake of House Calls.
- And then he grew up and
became Pernell Roberts.
- Okay, that's it.
Gypsy, did you realize
that Walter Pigeon was the
original Admiral Nelson
in the film version of
Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea?
- No way.
- Not Richard Basehart?
- Noooo!
- Crow, you are so cruel.
- So, letters?
- Terrible.
- Alright, alright.
Listen, this one is from Leslie
and it doesn't really
have a return address
but it's a real
nice picture of...
Me and Crow.
- Not really very good.
- Okay, come on,
you're coming with me.
- Ooh.
So, I'll just read this
other letter here, okay?
Hi, Cambot, put that up
on still store, would ya?
Ah well, sorry about
this, but you know
I can't hold up a picture.
Can't really hold up anything.
Arms don't work, you see,
they just kinda hang there.
Sad really.
So, this is from Mike
Ligett of Beaverton, Oregon
and it says, "I have reason
to believe that you are
"not really in space
broadcasting, but really
"broadcasting from Minnesota
or somewhere in the US,
"and your robots are
nothing but puppets."
Huh, real nice.
Takes all kinds to
make a world huh?
I'm Tom Servo reporting.
- [Crow] Mommy,
ow, whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Ooh, I didn't know
he could bend that far.
What do you think, sirs?
- I don't understand it, Frank.
This movie should have
broken their will,
it should have reduced Joel's
brain case to a peapod,
encouraged the bots to
rip their own heads off,
and yet they thrive on it.
They're growing
larger, more confident.
- You know, sometimes I
wish I was one of those
little guys up there,
quipping away, gadding about.
I wonder how you go to
the bathroom up in space?
- Frank, hand me my microphone.
Deep hurting!
- Poopie.
- [Forrester] Deep hurting!
- [Frank] Nooooo!
(slow somber theme music)